<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Musings | Wisdom Furnace</title>
    <link>https://www.wisdomfurnace.com/en/category/musings/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://www.wisdomfurnace.com/en/category/musings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Musings</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://www.wisdomfurnace.com/media/icon_hu46e1f2f25d3e9823056d1262581e76ae_28490_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Musings</title>
      <link>https://www.wisdomfurnace.com/en/category/musings/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Wisdom Furnace</title>
      <link>https://www.wisdomfurnace.com/en/post/welcome-to-wisdomfurnace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.wisdomfurnace.com/en/post/welcome-to-wisdomfurnace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-wisdom-furnace&#34;&gt;Welcome to Wisdom Furnace&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to welcoming you to this page, I want to express my gratitude. Thank you for reading my words and being willing to listen to why I started this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m 27 years old this year, but I feel that my heart doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem as mature as a 27-year-old. The old saying goes, &amp;ldquo;At thirty, one should stand firm&amp;rdquo;, I still have three years to go, but I don&amp;rsquo;t perceive such ability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the passage of time and the increase of age, I&amp;rsquo;m not willing to extinguish my enthusiasm in daily idleness and repetition. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be a person who is confused, doesn&amp;rsquo;t know where he came from, and even more doesn&amp;rsquo;t know where to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website will act as a thumbtack📌, pinning down information, knowledge, and thoughts. It will constantly remind me to think about three questions: where we come from, what changes we are in now, and where we should go in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;content-section-planning&#34;&gt;Content Section Planning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This website will initially focus on several sections. I hope to combine what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned and consult with professionals to learn and share the following contents:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Health-related knowledge, including common diseases and prevention, daily exercise injury protection, healthy diet and nutritional supplement suggestions, mental health maintenance, etc., to guide us to lay a solid foundation for a happy life;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some news, basic knowledge, and interesting cases in the field of economics and finance, guiding us to pursue economic independence and financial freedom;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some interesting cases about Chinese law, letting everyone know and understand the law, and become a person capable of protecting their own rights;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interesting tips for personal growth, life planning, time management, memory learning skills, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be determined&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The writing principles of these contents are: &lt;strong&gt;truth, objectivity, and beneficial&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;expectations-for-this-website&#34;&gt;Expectations for This Website&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope to keep it updated and let it become an important carrier to record the life trajectory and cognitive changes of me and my friends. I also hope this website can provide a place for my insightful friends who have many interesting stories to share but don&amp;rsquo;t have a platform, a place where they can chat, write, and share their opinions. Because I always believe, ideas become more interesting when they collide, and knowledge only generates value when shared and disseminated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the future, I hope to share our thoughts in more diverse forms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
